<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Connor Martin</title>
    <link>https://cjmartian.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Connor Martin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 13:00:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cjmartian.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bandit Coffee and Matcha</title>
      <link>https://cjmartian.github.io/bandit-coffee-and-matcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 13:00:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjmartian.github.io/bandit-coffee-and-matcha/</guid>
      <description>Bandit is a new coffee and matcha shop on North Lamar just past the river. Bandit has a wide selection of drinks and pastries to choose from along with a Lamar-facing patio to enjoy them on. Upon arrival they ask that you either download their app or use a provided kiosk to place your order in an attempt to maintain a contactless transaction which was highly appreciated.
Pictured (left to right) is an iced matcha latte, a hot latte, and an iced honey lavender matcha latte accompanied by a chocolate crescent and a blueberry doughnut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoodHeads</title>
      <link>https://cjmartian.github.io/foodheads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:43:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjmartian.github.io/foodheads/</guid>
      <description>FoodHeads is a mostly outdoor sandwich spot on North Guadalupe that features large sandwiches, iced tea, and made-in-kitchen soups. If you ever needed a reason to go get some rainy day comfort food, this is it. FoodHeads features a comfortable, quiet outdoor seating area where you can listen to birds nesting in a nearby birdhouse while you enjoy their food.
What drew me into this place was their Barbecue Bahn Mi (pictured).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try Hard Coffee</title>
      <link>https://cjmartian.github.io/try-hard-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 16:33:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cjmartian.github.io/try-hard-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Try Hard Coffee is currently undergoing some renivations, due to which they are currently serving their coffee out of a pop-up tent across the street in a local food truck park.
Regardless of where they are serving their coffee, they have a very interesting and unique selection of drinks to select from. Pictured is one latte, one iced latte, and a coffee cola (left to right) along with two cream puff pasteries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
